Md. Mahfuzur Rahman

+8801714583809

mahfuzur.rahman122@northsouth.edu

Ansari Monjil, KA-16, North Baridhara, Dhaka-1212

LinkedIn: http://bit.do/eRrMi
Date of Birth: 28 August, 1994



Career summary

A passionate Marketing Communications professional with experience in diversified fields including, key account management, content development & e-commerce operations.

Skills

- Strategic Campaign Planning
- Brand Management
- Content & Copy development

- MS Power Point
- Adobe Illustrator

Work Experiences

Year

Mediacom Limited - Member of Square Group

April, 2018 – Present

Account Executive, Client Relation

- Understand client's advertising requirements and submit the deliverables on time by collaborating with creative departments, production houses and others
- Develop strategic plans for clients

Clients:

- AFBL (Frutika, Farm Fresh),
- SFBL Local & International (Radhuni, Ruchi, Chashi, Chopstick, Aaram)

Campaigns

- Farm Fresh Pasteurized Milk "Khamar theke glass e"
- Frutika New Pack Launching
- Frutika Pure Soul Digital Campaign
- Farm Fresh UHT Thematic Campaign (about to launch)

Cooking Shows Planning & Execution

- All cooking shows of Radhuni, from 2018 to 2020
- Farm Fresh Weekly New Recipe 2019

Daraz Bangladesh

November, 2017 – April, 2018

Junior Executive, Operations

- Lead a 12 members team to manage order processing operations
- Solve issues and errors (ex. product missing, wrong shipping, double UID)

Cookie Jar

Intern, copywriting

- Develop contents for digital platforms
- Write story, creative copy & post copy for different brands

Educational Qualification		Year of passing
North South University		
BBA (Major in Marketing)		2017
Abdul Kadir Mollah City Co	ollege, Narsingdi	
HSC (Business Studies)		2011
Hasnabad High School		
SSC (Business Studies)		2009
Extra-Curricular Activiti	es	Year
NSUCDC Annual Drama 'Mo	olua Pala'	2015
Responsibilities: Acting, play	ring musical instruments & perfor	ming at flash mob
Workshop Drama 'Bhoote	r Talk Show'	2015
Responsibilities: Acting & sto	age setup	
Courses	Year of certification	on earned/Course status
Presentation Skills: Speecl	nwriting, Slides and Delivery	2020
		Number of Courses: 4
Negotiation, Mediation and	2020	

Advertising and Society by Duke University on Coursera

2020

Number of Courses: 4

Course Topics

History of advertising; subliminal advertising & ethics; sexuality in advertising;

Google Analytics Certification by Google Inc.

by ESSEC Business School on Coursera

2017

References

	Cynthia McKinney	Md. Simon Islam Shawon
	Lecturer, Political Science	Account Director, Client Relation
	North South University	Mediacom Ltd Member of Square Group
Email: cynthia.northsouth.edu@gmail.com		Mobile Number: +8801713851931
		Email: simon@mediacombd.com